hot-people.info 2015-12-30

# Hot People

The privacy of visitors to www.Hot-People.info (also the Site or Hot People) is important to us. At the Site we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit the Site, and how we safeguard your information. 

### Log Files

We collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup advertisement or window, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on the Site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Hot People may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Hot People website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit Hot People website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, dispute procedures, and application of Virginia state law.

### Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 1, 2010.
